Charles Scribner's Sons Art Reference Department
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Miscellaneous Reference Files, 1933-1952, undated, Series 3:; (Box 6, 8, OV 12; 1.0 linear feet)
  These files contain original art work, photographs, and printed material concerning miscellaneous reference topics. The files concerning Ancient Art and The Bible contain portraits of various saints and historic individuals and photographs of historic sites.
  The New York City file includes early photographs of the Scribner Building, the Custom House and Bowling Green, the Times Building, the Postal Telegraph Building, Federal Hall in snow, the New York Stock Exchange, the Metropolitan Museum of Art, the Washington Square Arch, Grant's Tomb, the Presbyterian Hospital, and St. Patrick's Cathedral. There is also a photograph of the construction of the Flatiron Building and an aerial photograph of the Flatiron Building.
  - Airplanes, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ancient Art, undated, (6 folders) (Box 6, Folder 11-16)
  - Austria, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Bible, undated, (10 folders; Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 18-27)
  - The Bible, undated, (10 folders; Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 28-37)
  - The Bible, undated, (10 folders; Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 38-47)
  - The Bible, undated, (10 folders; Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 48-57)
  - The Bible, undated, (7 folders; Oversized items housed in OV 12) (Box 6, Folder 58-64)
  - Buildings, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Burma, undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Chicago World's Fair, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Clothing, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Connecticut, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 69-70)
  - Crafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - French Cathedral, 1952, (negatives only; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Greece, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - New York City, undated, (6 folders; oversized items housed in Box 8) (Box 6, Folder 74-79)
  - Romania, undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Virginia, undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Five Photographs of Art Work and Miscellaneous Views of New York City, undated, (Scanned with Box 6, F74-79) (Box 8 (sol))
  - Oversized Photograph of Painting of Mary and the Christ Child, undated, (Scanned with Box 6, F18-24) (Box OV 12)